He's fighting a war he doesn't believe in, hoping to find something he does.
Savior is a history, drama, war film directed by Predrag Antonijević.
A hardened mercenary in the Foreign Legion begins to find his own humanity
when confronted with atrocities during the fighting in Bosnia.
Joshua Rose, played by Dennis Quaid.
Paris Priest, played by Pascal Rollin.
Christian, played by Catlin Foster.
Peter, played by Stellan Skarsgård.
Colonel, played by John Maclaren.
Vera, played by Nataša Ninković.
Savior is a 1998 American war film starring Dennis Quaid, Stellan
Skarsgård, Nastassja Kinski, and Nataša Ninković.
It is about a U.S.
mercenary escorting a Bosnian Serb woman and her newborn child to a
United Nations safe zone during the Bosnian War.
It was produced by Oliver Stone.
The film explores themes of rape, civil war, mercenary, serbian, atrocity.
The tone is emotional.